[Love Between Lines]
[Episode 2]
♪ What identity do you use
to enter and exit the role? ♪
♪ Reality and fantasy
are parallel and intertwine ♪
♪ About the characters
and relationships of love ♪
Everyone, welcome to Rongcheng.
The blizzard has blocked the roads.
♪ Like a multifaceted gem,
obsessed with each side ♪
Distinguished guests,
you'll have to
temporarily stay in Rongcheng.
♪ Time and space interlace;
it's still you ♪
♪ Love overlaps in destiny ♪
[15 minutes ago]
♪ You made me change
my impromptu promise ♪
♪ Two hearts slowly get closer
amidst sparks ♪
This is exactly what I needed.
Anna, (Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
financial advisor from Side M.
Your mission in Rongcheng
is to help Qin Xiaoyi
become the new mayor of Rongcheng
and gain his trust.
You must beat others
in convincing Qin Xiaoyi
to sign the policy contract.
However,
you have a secret past.
A few years ago,
you were saved by Ning Zechen.
In order to repay him,
your real mission
is to help Ning Zechen become the mayor.
The box of rouge
is your token of recognition.
He will provide evidence
to frame Qin Xiaoyi.
♪ To heal each other ♪
But your identity as a mole
must not be discovered by Qin Xiaoyi.
Please proceed with caution.
Let's go.
Who are you?
Let's talk, Chief Ning.
You're Anna.
Long time no see, Chief Ning.
It's such an old thing.
I'm surprised you still have it.
Anna,
have you been well abroad
these past years?
I have to put on this reunion act?
I've been alright.
Ten years since we parted.
On life's journey,
we meet again.
Oh please!
Why are you reciting poetry now?
Let bygones be bygones.
W-What does that mean?
It means
"move on from the past."
Hurry and give me
the evidence to frame Qin Xiaoyi.
Only then can we move forward together.
So, stop talking and give it to me.
And give me a handgun too.
Nothing else, right?
Money.
You're robbing me.
Ms. Anna,
I have high hopes for you,
but if General Qin finds out about this,
as the Police Chief, I cannot...
Got it.
[General's Office]
Come in.
I thought I'd acted early enough.
Which side are you on?
You're here to steal things.
I'm here to plant things.
Same objective.
What are you talking about?
We're each doing our own tasks.
Understand?
Listen.
Don't tell anyone you've seen us.
Fine.
Okay.
What?
Qin Xiaoyi is coming?
Okay, we'll leave right now.
Okay, okay.
Hey...
Is it appropriate
to take out a phone here?
Look.
It's just a game.
Don't take things so seriously.
Let's go.
Go!
Stop!
What?
Let her go!
I...
After them!
General Qin,
don't you know to secure your own things?
Someone broke into your office
to steal files.
I tried to help,
and this is my outcome?
I can see
you've tried very hard.
Thank you.
No, I can do it myself.
Of course.
You two,
go check my office.
See if anything is missing
or
if anything new has appeared.
Yes, sir.
General,
a document is missing,
but
nothing new has appeared.
The office is so messy.
He'll definitely tidy it up later.
If I hide something here now,
it'll be discovered quickly.
Not only will I fail to frame him,
but I'll become the suspect instead.
Not bad.
You dodged a bullet.
General Qin,
I don't know what you're talking about.
I want to invite you
to come in.
Please have a seat.
Wasn't your file stolen?
Why aren't you going after them?
There are
no important documents to steal here.
Everything's hidden elsewhere.
How scheming.
I'm complimenting your intelligence.
Then why are you here?
I'm a financial advisor for Side M.
I'm here to discuss a partnership
with you.
As long as
you sign this contract...
Once it's signed...
And the contract is sent back to M,
the promised funds
will be transferred immediately.
General Qin, I know
you want to be the mayor.
I can help you.
I understand what you mean,
but if you want me to sign this contract,
you need to show me your sincerity.
What kind of sincerity?
Is it still about that formula?
Wait!
General Qin,
I know what you want.
Tonight at 10,
meet me at the dance hall.
Everything is ready.
You just need the final push.
General Qin,
I'll give you
this final push.
It seems all the plot missions
are pre-designed.
I got the formula here last time too.
So, I just need to...
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop!
What are you doing?
I'm robbing you of a letter!
General Qin,
may I have this dance?
I'm sorry.
Seems I've offered
the wrong token of sincerity.
Ms. Anna.
This
contains the formula
for manufacturing arms.
Before Sun Jiaying could get it,
I intercepted it.
General Qin,
are you satisfied?
As we agreed before,
I show you my sincerity,
and you sign the contract with me.
It seems that you have
some misunderstandings about me.
I don't
accept negotiations.
Well, that's unfortunate then.
General Qin,
have you made your decision?
General Qin, then I'll take my leave.
Take her away.
Qin Xiaoyi, you broke your promise!
You...
Did I ever promise you anything?
I know
there are spies around me
planted by others.
Hey,
if you don't trust me,
why ask me for the formula?
All's fair in war.
Besides,
what you gave me
probably isn't the real formula, is it?
[Those who seek revenge are gentlemen]
To lure me into your trap,
you have gone to great lengths.
What a pity.
General Qin...
General Qin!
I...
General Qin...
If you kill me now,
you'll never get the formula.
You said before
you only focus on what you want.
And right now,
I'm the only one who knows where it is.
Then what do you want?
I want to live.
Not being a gentleman anymore?
I can't afford to be one now,
can I?
Eleven o'clock
Rongda Casino.
It'll be your last chance.
Just keep waiting.
No.
He's already impatient.
What if the waiting
makes him annoyed
and he leaves?
Ms. Anna,
please come with me.
It's over.
Sun Jiaying works for him.
He's here to settle scores with me.
Apologies,
Ms. Anna.
If you hand over the formula,
perhaps I can spare your life.
Chief Feng, you misunderstood.
You should know
I don't have such a thing.
Ms. Anna,
I know you want to join Qin Xiaoyi's side,
but he's paranoid.
He has so many collaborators.
You're not important to him at all,
Ms. Anna.
Since you refuse to
hand over the formula...
Execute her.
[Economic Cooperation Agreement]
-Big!
-Small!
Again!
I still can't win.
Then what do you want?
I want to live.
Not being a gentleman anymore?
I can't afford to be one now,
can I?
Ms. Anna,
tell me
the formula is still in your possession
and not taken by Feng Youjin.
Of course.
Why did you drop those hawthorn balls?
Were you so certain
I would come to save you?
General Qin,
I wouldn't dare bet on that with you.
I left the hawthorn balls
just to let you know
that I went to the casino
and didn't break my promise.
Did you need to waste
so many hawthorn balls
just to prove you went to the casino?
Ms. Anna,
give me the formula.
And I'll take it as
you keeping your promise.
Don't worry,
I'll take you to get it right now.
After I got the formula,
I hid it
under the container
next to the post office.
The most dangerous place
is also the safest place.
Exactly.
They must have followed us here.
We need to leave quickly.
General Qin,
please hand over the formula.
I did receive a document,
but it doesn't have
your name on it.
It seems what you want
is more than just a simple document.
Since you refuse to
hand over the formula...
Execute her.
Wait!
Chief Feng,
I can ally with anyone,
but the only person I want to defeat
is Qin Xiaoyi.
He knows I have the formula
and will definitely
come looking for me here.
I'll lead him to the formula.
If you want to know where it's hidden,
you should know what to do.
Interesting.
Ms. Anna,
well done.
I was at the end of my rope.
Won't you allow me to
find a way out of a desperate situation?
Finding a way out of
a desperate situation.
Good courage.
I miscalculated.
But the game isn't over yet.
I hope in today's match,
you'll have the last laugh.
I will.
When the mayor's election comes,
I invite you to sit in the audience
and see clearly
who the final winner really is.
♪ Think about you ♪
Take him away.
♪ Care about you ♪
♪ Goodnight to you ♪
♪ All night long for you ♪
♪ Think about you ♪
♪ Care about you ♪
Ning Zechen and his team
won the final victory!
♪ Goodnight to you ♪
♪ All night long for you ♪
♪ Think about you ♪
♪ Care about you ♪
♪ Goodnight to you ♪
♪ All night long for you ♪
Where is he?
♪ Think about you ♪
♪ All night long for you ♪
Today is Member's Day.
Free water available.
Please help yourselves.
Remember to replenish electrolytes
after exercising.
What's this for?
This?
It's for you to leave messages
for your favorite NPC.
Although we don't recommend
players and NPCs
having too much off-game contact,
you can use this method
to express your support and love.
I can only express my support and love?
It's not appropriate
to write negative comments here, is it?
Thank you.
[The fox can't be the winner here. -Anna]
[Mr. Xu]
Mr. Xu.
Why did you suddenly cancel my leave?
Do we have a new client?
It's not a new client.
We have
a new team member joining us.
Come here, Shuaishuai.
Shuaishuai.
Come here.
I've noticed you're quite free every day.
Take it to the pet salon this afternoon.
Come, come.
Good.
Mr. Xu.
I joined the company right after college.
I originally wanted to
be an architect.
You said you needed
an assistant who understood architecture,
so you had me fill the spot temporarily
and said you'd transfer me
to the design department later.
That's right.
It's been three years.
What about that transfer?
Hu.
That's not the right way to put it.
I've already transferred you.
Think about it.
You used to be an assistant.
And now?
You're the general manager's assistant.
Right?
Isn't that right?
Hu.
The company
doesn't have many projects now.
We don't need designers at the moment.
Wait until we secure
another big client this year—
"Once we secure
a few more big clients this year,
"I'll definitely transfer you.
"Young people shouldn't be too impatient,
"or you'll end up at a disadvantage."
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
As your assistant,
I take to heart
everything you say.
I'll head out now.
I was at the end of my rope.
Won't you allow me to
find a way out of a desperate situation?
I hope in today's game,
you'll have the last laugh.
Mr. Xu.
What is it now?
I'm quitting.
Quitting?
Before I quit, let me warn you:
it's best not to drink that coffee.
Last month, several employees
in our department said
they found dead cockroaches
when cleaning the coffee machine.
How many was it?
Two or three?
Hu, why didn't you
tell me about this earlier?
I think there were four, Mr. Xu!
Zhao,
I was just using that to fool my boss...
No, my former boss.
Why do you actually believe that?
Hu Xiu, how did I never notice
that you're actually crazy?
Crazy?
I love that title.
Thanks for the compliment.
So you've decided to quit
without another job lined up?
You don't have any backup plans
for yourself.
It would be so much better
if you found another job before quitting.
Zhao.
Do you know what happens to someone
who stays with a bad option
while looking for better ones?
They end up spending their whole life
on that bad option without realizing it.
So,
I have to push myself
to start over fresh.
Start over fresh?
You mean...
I still want to be an architect.
Are you sure?
Then I support you
with all my heart.
You're so strong.
You're just too weak.
Who is it?
Don't look.
A murder mystery game?
There's a game in half an hour.
Going again? Didn't you win last time?
The fox didn't witness it last time.
It wasn't a perfect victory.
I'm off.
Fox?
Is that a new character?
This way please.
♪ Life lays out the outline of my scenes ♪
So beautiful.
♪ The last act
was a monologue in a dream ♪
♪ And in the next,
I wander through the city's noise ♪
♪ So many arrivals
that turned out to be nothing ♪
♪ I'm counting the beats of the clock ♪
♪ I can't tell which platform
is for leaving or returning ♪
♪ Until you walk toward me ♪
Everyone, welcome
to Rongcheng.
[Group B Warlord Commander Qin Xiaoyi]
The current situation in Rongcheng
is extremely complicated.
Chief Feng
has already established cooperation
with Pavlovich,
while Director Lin
has Mr. Kobayashi backing him.
Anna,
today,
if we can reach an agreement
and I get the support
from M's headquarters,
then I
will definitely lead you
to ultimate victory.
Anna!
This Qin Xiaoyi is so over-the-top.
Ms. Anna.
I'm sorry.
I'll think about
this cooperation some more.
Anna, Anna!
I don't think you understand what I mean.
If you have any concerns,
feel free to bring them up.
We will achieve victory.
Trust me.
This contract...
You can take it.
But, General Qin,
being too eager
only makes me doubt your abilities.
If you want me to sign this contract,
you need to show me your sincerity.
Wait a minute.
I don't quite understand what you mean.
What kind of sincerity
are you looking for?
How many candied hawthorns
would I need to eat
to make the 600 yuan worth it?
Let me go!
I've been framed! I've been framed!
Anna,
I'm so disappointed in you!
Anna!
Likewise.
Hello.
How come today's Qin Xiaoyi
is different from before?
We have two groups of actors, A and B.
They perform in rotation.
I see.
Do you have a schedule for the two groups?
Yes, we do,
but the actor you want to see
is our special guest performer.
His work schedule is not fixed.
I don't know the details either.
Take care.
These aren't the same messages as before.
That makes sense.
They'll run out of room
if they don't switch them out.
Can it read my mind?
Does anyone know Qin Xiaoyi's real name?
All the other NPC actors
created social media accounts.
Only he's being mysterious.
He's not even on the official cast list.
I have a friend who used to work there.
Even he couldn't find any information.
They say he doesn't like public attention.
He's just an NPC actor.
It's not like he's some big celebrity.
Why be so mysterious?
Probably just a marketing strategy.
Whether it's a strategy or not,
the other actor is really not as good.
Indeed,
he's not quite as good.
Mr. Gong,
I need to tell you something.
Qin Xiaoyi from Group A
hasn't been coming these days.
Today, there was even a player
who specifically asked about his sessions.
Okay, I got it.
Hello, sir.
Do you have a reservation?
Yes,
I'm waiting for a friend.
Mr. Xiao.
My friend.
This way, please.
Been quite busy these days?
Looking for apartments everywhere.
No wonder you haven't been to the club.
Wait, if you're looking for apartments,
you can just have your agent
do the legwork.
Why are you going personally?
The rental situation there is special.
There are a lot of shared spaces.
The landlords want to
meet tenants before renting.
What's wrong?
I know you're busy.
You can come to the club
whenever you want.
It's just that...
An employee just called me.
He said there was a player today
who specifically asked about Qin Xiaoyi
and the schedule for Groups A and B.
Seems like they came just for you.
I'm just mentioning it.
But Xiao, don't worry.
When we first opened this club,
we agreed on everything.
It absolutely won't affect your work.
Your schedule and information
are completely confidential.
You won't have any private contact
with players.
Rest assured.
Take a good look
who the final winner really is.
[Qin Xiaoyi]
This is no problem at all.
Sure, sure.
It's just ahead.
This way.
Granny Chen.
Granny Chen!
I've brought a client
to see the apartment.
Excuse us.
Come in.
Thank you.
Here, watch your step.
It's fine.
Alright, it's fine.
The path is uneven. Take it slow.
Okay, don't worry.
Don't worry about me.
Just hold onto your things.
Coming to see Xiu?
You're back?
Yes, yes.
Watch out.
Where should I put this?
Young man,
how long are you planning to rent for?
I haven't decided yet,
so I'd like to rent by month.
Take it easy.
In...
Ex-in-law.
Don't call us that.
We don't deserve that title.
Is Xiu not here?
So, you're living in this house now?
This is all my family's property!
Why should an outsider
care who lives here?
I'm just asking if she's here.
Why are you shouting?
Don't worry.
Living here
is very convenient and comfortable.
All the neighbors
have been here for years.
Everyone gets along well with each other.
First, get that irresponsible son of yours
to come back to Shanghai
and apologize in person.
What do you mean irresponsible?
What's wrong with my son?
Is breaking up being irresponsible?
These days, people date
and break up all the time, okay?
What was he doing before this?
Did he have to do it at this point?
And now, he's not even coming back.
What kind of man is that?
Alright, alright.
Keep your voice down.
The neighbors are watching.
Well,
Normally,
the soundproofing
is quite effective, right?
That's Mr. Hu's daughter.
She was planning to get married,
but for some reason,
the groom ran away
on their engagement day.
If you ask me,
she's right to yell at him.
Um, Granny,
this is a special situation, right?
It's not usually this noisy.
It's not like this normally.
Your son broke off the engagement!
And you have the nerve
to come to our house, demanding answers
and wanting the first-meeting gift back?
I've never seen anything like this.
Let's break up peacefully
and part on good terms.
What's wrong with
settling accounts clearly?
Or would you like everyone
to judge who's right?
Hey!
Mom, Dad.
Xiu, you're here.
Don't be angry.
Go inside.
I'll talk to her.
Calm down.
Getting angry is bad for your health.
Come inside quickly.
Auntie,
if you want
the first-meeting gift money back,
that's fine.
But I remember
when my parents first met Zhang Qiran,
they also gave him a gift
based on what you gave me.
Both sides are even,
yet you're demanding money today.
What's the logic in that?
That was received by Qiran.
It never went through my hands.
What about the engagement banquet?
You don't argue about that.
My parents upgraded the venue.
You didn't even mention the cost
and that's fine,
but you immediately added
another table for your relatives.
She has the nerve to ask for money?
Exactly.
You seem
more pitiful than me,
who got dumped.
I will never have
anything to do with your son
for the rest of my life.
But you and that kind of person
will probably be tied together forever.
Auntie,
I'll see you out one last time.
If you're looking for a short-term rental,
it's indeed a bit troublesome.
As soon as I hear from Granny Chen,
I'll let you know immediately.
Okay.
Please move.
Xiu!
Coming.
Oh, please.
Control your temper, will you?
Xiu lives here.
If you make a scene everywhere,
how can she continue living here?
Really.
Mom, Dad.
I'm sorry.
It's all because of me.
That's not right.
How could this be your fault?
It's like walking down the street
and stepping in dog poop
someone left behind.
You can't blame yourself
for your bad luck.
We're eating here.
Fine, I'll stop talking.
Here.
Have some soup.
Come sit down.
You should go back to work now.
You can't stay on vacation
at home forever.
This isn't right.
Besides,
no matter what,
your current job is quite stable.
We'll find you an even better man later.
He'll definitely be better
than that Zhang guy.
Right?
Dad,
actually, I've already qu...
What's wrong?
It hurts.
I think it's going to rain
in a couple of days.
What did you just say?
What's wrong?
I've made up my mind.
I'm fine. I'll work hard.
I just saw my parents off.
My mom brought you some side dishes.
Thank her for me.
I guess they're finally relieved now.
Did you tell them
about your job?
It's okay.
Once you find a new job in a few days,
they won't say anything about it.
I have to go to
the park managers' meeting tonight.
Talk to you later.
♪ I saw the tram
driving under the sunset ♪
♪ Like walking into a pause in a summer ♪
The distance of the glass wall
needs to be recalculated.
Send me the 3D model tomorrow.
♪ At this moment, the sunset is gentle ♪
♪ I look up and press the shutter ♪
♪ I take a bit of your city as a memory ♪
Mr. Xiao.
The technical director is over there.
Follow me.
♪ Leaving a hurried silhouette
for the dusk ♪
♪ Talking about random topics ♪
♪ Waiting for the traffic light at dusk ♪